incredibleforum.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy

## Forum Foundry Privacy Policy // Last Updated: 12/14/2011

##### 1\. Purpose

Forum Foundry, Inc. owns and operates a number of website properties, including forum / community type properties. Forum Foundry, Inc. has adopted this Privacy Statement in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from this website or from websites operated by Forum Foundry. Your use of the websites constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement and your consent to the practices it describes.

##### 2\. Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information

When you visit Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s), like when you visit most other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (such as “aol.com” or “earthlink.net”), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at Forum Foundry, Inc. website properties, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to the Forum Foundry, Inc. website. This information is not personally identifiable.

##### 3\. Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address or any information you submitted to the Forum Foundry Inc. website that identifies you individually.

Forum Foundry, Inc. will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want Forum Foundry, Inc. to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.

You can visit and browse Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s) without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. Forum Foundry, Inc. may collect personally identifiable information about you from its website by methods such as the following:

##### 4\. Registration Forms

If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion or to become a registered user of a Forum Foundry, Inc. website, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and/or a unique individual password.

##### 5\. Transactions and Activity

If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s), it collects information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and your other activity on the site. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the website that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amount and payment information.

##### 6\. Email and other voluntary communications

You may also choose to communicate with Forum Foundry, Inc. through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.

##### 7\. Information Use

Forum Foundry, Inc. may use the personally identifiable information collected through its website primarily for such purposes as:  
a) helping to establish and verify the identity of users;  
b) opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users’ accounts or memberships;  
c) processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;  
d) providing services and support to users;  
e) improving the website, including tailoring it to users’ preferences;  
f) providing users with service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about Forum Foundry, Inc.;  
g) responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;  
h) maintaining the security and integrity of its systems.

Forum Foundry, Inc. uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its website. Forum Foundry, Inc. may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its website to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.

##### 8\. Disclosure of Information

Forum Foundry, Inc. does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. Forum Foundry, Inc. may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its website or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. Forum Foundry, Inc. may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, as Forum Foundry, Inc.’s business develops, it may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. If Forum Foundry, Inc., its internet businesses, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, customer information may be one of the assets transferred.

##### 9\. “Cookies” and Advertisers

Forum Foundry, Inc. website server(s), or the servers of companies that are used to operate this site, may place a “cookie” on your computer in order to allow you to use the website and to personalize your experience.

A “cookie” is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s) to recognize your computer while you are on its website and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website.

The advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on this website may also use cookies that are not sent by Forum Foundry, Inc.’s website(s). Such ads or content may contain cookies that help track and target the interests of users of this website in order to present “personalized” advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. Forum Foundry, Inc. is not responsible for any such cookies.

Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website.

##### 10\. Security

Forum Foundry, Inc. maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the site, transaction information is transmitted to and from Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s) in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Forum Foundry, Inc. restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

##### 11\. Choice/Opt-Out

In order to provide service to you, Forum Foundry, Inc. will send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of its website. From time to time, Forum Foundry, Inc. may also wish to send you updates about Forum Foundry, Inc. or promotions. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from Forum Foundry, Inc. properties, please send an email containing your request to support@forumfoundry.com

##### 12\. Data Quality/Access

Forum Foundry, Inc. allows you to change, update, or delete the information you may provide in your optional registration form. If you would like to change, update, or delete your personal information, please send an email containing your request to support@forumfoundry.com

##### 13\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Forum Foundry, Inc. reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Forum Foundry, Inc. will post a link to the new policy on its website. In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this written policy shall control.

##### 14\. Contacting Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the information practices of Forum Foundry, Inc., please contact us by email at support@forumfoundry.com

##### 15\. Governing law.

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by California law. Any claim related to the Site or this policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in California, within one year after the claim arises. You agree no such claim may be brought as a class action. Users of Forum Foundry, Inc. website(s) consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy. Forum Foundry, Inc. is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer.

##### 16\. Children.

Forum Foundry, Inc. does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Forum Foundry, Inc. has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at support@forumfoundry.com

##### 17\. Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements.

Forum Foundry, Inc. expects its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Forum Foundry, Inc. website page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Forum Foundry, Inc. you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Forum Foundry, Inc. is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

##### 18\. Third Party Ad Servers.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer web site at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
